{
    "question": "Minta tolong kasi contoh percakapan bahasa inggris tentang pernyataan setuju dan tidak setuju",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Class Vacation<br><br><span>Yoga\t: So, class. Now we are going to deliberate our concern about where we are going to head for our class vacation. So, who comes up with the idea first?<br>Habibi\t: I will vote for Anyer Beach. Anyer Beach is one of the nearest beaches we can visit.<br>Yoga\t: So, class. Is there anyone who disagrees with Anyer Beach?<br>Jenny\t: Um, I am not sure about that. Last vacation our class had gone to Anyer Beach. I think we should see other options.<br>Habibi\t: Oh yeah! You\u2019re right, I forgot about that.<br>Jefri\t: Well, I\u2019m suggesting Kebun Raya Bogor<br>Kania\t: I agree with you, Jefri. I have never been there myself.<br>Geri\t: Me too, I am with you, Kania. Seeing great trees and plants must be exciting. Kebun Raya Bogor is like a great jungle in the middle of town.<br>Sarah\t: I\u2019m sorry guys. I think I will disagree with that. It\u2019s rainy season now. And as you know, Kebun Raya Bogor is located in Bogor which is the city of rain. And seeing the intensity of rainfall throughout Indonesia lately, I think we might not be able to explore the whole Kebun Raya Bogor due to the rain.<br>Tio\t: I think what Sarah said is right. Kebun Raya Bogor is not the best place to visit during this heavy rainy season<br>Yoga\t: Well, are there any other options?<br>Fauzi\t: How about Bali?<br>Habibi\t: No way! I don\u2019t have enough money to go to Bali<br>Sarah\t: Habibi is right, Fauzi. It\u2019s really costly to pick Bali as an option.<br>Yoga\t: Okay, class. To save the time, now let\u2019s just write your idea into a piece of paper and we will deliberate in the next occasion. Thank you.<br><br>contoh yang lebih simple lagi :)<br><br></span>A : hi, good morning B<br>B : morning A, how are you??<br>A : i&#039;m fine thank&#039;s<br>B : are you agree if i break up with C??<br>A : no, i don&#039;t<br>B : why??<br>A : I&#039;m not agree if you break up with C, because she more Love you then anyone, bro don&#039;t break up with her, and maybe sometime you can&#039;t find girl like C anymore, so don&#039;t break up with her<br>B : uhh, okay broooo, thank&#039;s for that<br><span>A : your welcome dude....<br></span><br>sekian dari saya :D",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lin :I can&#039;t help to hold on any longer.<br>Sara : Oh why?<br>Lin : I think he truly never cares about me. He keeps talking about his ex-girl friend and it hurts me. He doesn&#039;t love me anymore!<br>Sara : <em>I don&#039;t think so</em>, Lin! Jey does love you so much. I know it. You&#039;re everything to him. Probably he did that just want to know how your response is. He wants to know whether you love him as he loves you. Ask him yourself and keep positive thinking. Don&#039;t ever let him go because of your emotion.<br>Lin : <em><strong>I think you&#039;re right</strong></em>. It might be better to talk to him directly. Thanks, Sara.<br>Sara : you are very welcome.<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858",
            "question": "Whats is the problem from the story \"Snow Bride\"",
            "attachments": [
                "question-attachments/whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858-1.docx"
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Carilah kata-kata yang terdengar janggal dan aneh... :)Mandiri lebih baik.<br>Okay ? @Liwed",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-contoh-pecakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pemesanan-meja-di-618",
            "question": "Buatlah contoh pecakapan bahasa inggris tentang pemesanan meja di restoran..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i want to ask permission<br>B: yes of course<br>A: two days there will be an event in my home, can i order 2 pieces of table<br>B: of course may be happy<br>A: ok i&#039;ll wait for tomorrow<br>B: okay, thank you&#039;ve booked a table here<br>A: you&#039;re welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>A: Good afternoon <br>b: Good afternoon, can I help you? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table, for tomorrow afternoon? <br>b: yes, it could. for how many people? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table for lunch two people! <br>B: Yes sir, tomorrow daytime table number five <br>A: Thank you<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expressions-of-surprise-untuk-dua-orang-622",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "put-the-verb-in-the-brackets-into-the-correct-form-examples-i-did-144",
            "question": "Put the verb in the brackets into the correct form    examples\r\ni didn't go (not/go) to work yesterday because i wasn't (not/be) very well\r\n\r\n1.last week our teacher__(not/come) to\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0class because he__(be)very well\r\n2.his grandfather__(not/meet) me when he__(be)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0in jakarta\r\n3.i__(not/understand) what he said\r\n4.i__(not/have) to go to work yesterday\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0because \u00a0it__(be) a holiday\r\n5.they__(watch) the football match on TV\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0this morning",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "last week our teacher didn&#039;t came to the class he wasn&#039;t very well<br>his grandfather didn&#039;t met me when he was in jakarta<br>I didn&#039;t understand what he said<br>I haven&#039;t to go to work yesterday because it was a holiday<br>They watched the football match on TV this morning<br><br>maaf ya kalau ada yang keliru atau salah :)",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "\u00a01.last week our teacher didn&#039;t come\u00a0(not/come) to<br>\u00a0 \u00a0class because he wasn&#039;t\u00a0(be\u00a0)very well<br>2.his grandfather didn&#039;t meet\u00a0(not/meet) me when he wasn&#039;t(be)<br>\u00a0 \u00a0in jakarta<br>3.i doesn&#039;t\u00a0(not/understand) what he said<br>4.i didn&#039;t\u00a0(not/have) to go to work yesterday<br>\u00a0 \u00a0because \u00a0it wasn&#039;t\u00a0(be) a holiday<br>5.they watch\u00a0(watch) the football match on TV<br><span>\u00a0 \u00a0this morning</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-artinya-shawty-182",
            "question": "Apa artinya shawty ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "shawty itu bahasa slang-nya bhs inggris yang artinya cantik,menarik.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-bantuannya-jelaskan-pengertian-spoof-text-dan-contohnya-899",
            "question": "Tolong bantuannya, jelaskan pengertian spoof text dan contohnya, trmksh",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Spoof Text, Penjelasan + Contoh Lengkap- Pernahkah kalian melihat salah satu program komedi, Seketsa? Pastinya kalian tidak asing kan. Jalan cerita di Seketsa itu lah yang dinamakanSpoof Text. Awal cerita dimulai dengan adegan atau kejadian yang biasa kemudian menjelang akhir ada adegan atau kejadian yang tidak dikira yang membuat cerita tersebut lucu.<br><br>Untuk melengkapi penjelasan mengenai\u00a0Jenis Teks Bahasa Inggris (Types of Text), pada kesempatan kali ini penulis hadirkan penjelasan dan contoh\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0lengkap.<br><br>A. Pengertian Spoof Text<br><br>Selain\u00a0Narrative Text,\u00a0Recount Text, dan\u00a0Anecdote Text,\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0juga termasuk ke dalam golongan\u00a0Narration\u00a0(lihat\u00a0Jenis Teks Bahasa Inggris,\u00a0Types of Text), yang tentunya menceritakan kejadian di masa lampau dengan akhir yang lucu dan tidak disangka-sangka.<br><br>B. Tujuan Komunikatif Spoof Text<br><br>Tentunya semua jenis teks yang tergolong\u00a0Narration\u00a0memiliki tujuan komunikatif yang sama, begitu juga pada\u00a0Spoof Text, yaitu untuk menghibur pembaca atau pendengar dari cerita yang dibacakan.<br><br>C. Struktur Kebahasaan Spoof Text<br><br>Terdapat tiga jenis struktur kebahasaan yang dimiliki oleh\u00a0Spoof Text, yaitu:<br><br>1. Orientation<br><br>Seperti halnya jenis teks\u00a0Narration\u00a0yang lain, selalu diawali dengan\u00a0orientation.\u00a0Orientationadalah bagian di mana penulis memulai memperkenalkan cerita.<br><br>2. Events<br><br>Sedangkan pada bagian\u00a0Events\u00a0yaitu bagian di mana penulis menceritakan kejadian-kejadian dalam cerita tersebut tetapi kejadian yang diceritakan masih kejadian yang wajar.<br><br>3. Twist\u00a0<br><br>Dan bagian dari\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0yang terakhir adalah\u00a0Twist.\u00a0Twist\u00a0merupakan bagian teks yang mana menceritakan kebalikan dari kejadian-kejadian wajar di bagian\u00a0Events.\u00a0Twistmerupakan bagian akhir dari\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0yang menceritakan kejadian akhir lucu dan tidak disangka-sangka sebelumnya.\u00a0<br><br>D. Ciri Kebahasaan Spoof Text<br><br>Terdapat beberapa ciri kebahasaan\u00a0Spoof Text\u00a0yang bisa membedakan dengan\u00a0Jenis Teks Bahasa Inggris (Types of Text)\u00a0yang lainnya, yaitu:<br><br>1. Menggunakan\u00a0Past Tense; was, were, did, etc.<br><br>2. Menggunakan kata kerja aksi (action verb);\u00a0did, went, walked, etc.<br><br>3. Menggunakan kata keterangan waktu dan kata keterangan tempat.<br><br>4. Diceritakan secara kronologis.</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "spoof text adalah jenis teks yang menceritakan kejadian masa lalu yang lucu dan terjadinya tidak terprediksi.<br>contohnya cerita tentang hal konyol yang kamu alami seperti terpeleset di depan umum, dsb<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-soal-persuading-195",
            "question": "Contoh soal soal persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Why don\u2019t you\ntry our special drink bandrek to warm up your body?\n\n\n\n\n<br><span>\nIf I were you, I\nwould \u2026 ?</span>\n<span>\n\u00a0I\u2019m sure you are\non the right track.?</span>\n\n\n<br><span>\n\u00a0<span>I bet you could\ndo it.?</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "22-milyar-dalam-mata-uang-dolar-senilai-dengan-210-663",
            "question": "2,2 milyar dalam mata uang dolar senilai dengan ?........\r\n$\u00a0210,000\r\natau 2,2 billion ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Billion = Milyar<br>Million = Juta<br>Tetapi, bila 2,2 milyar rupiah dibuat ke dalam dolar, maka sekitar $210,000. Karena dolar dengan rupiah kan lebih tinggi dolar...",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "yaitu, senilai dengan $210,000<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "soal-all-these-year-dinas-family-in-poverty-a-has-485",
            "question": "Soal : all these year , Dina's family.......... in poverty    a. has lived\u00a0\r\nb. was living\u00a0\r\nc. lives\u00a0\r\nd. has been living\r\ne. lived\u00a0\r\n\r\ntolong sertai dengan penjelasan ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "yang bener jawaban D kalo menurutku. Itu termasuk kalimat Present Perfect Continuous Tense yang rumusnya S + have/has + been + Ving. Tujuan teks itu adalah untuk menyatakan suatu kegiatan yang dimulai pada waktu lampau tetapi masih berlangsung sampai sekarang bahkan ada kemungkinan akan terus berlangsung. Clue nya itu phrase \"All these years\"<br><br>menurutku sih begitu\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}